[
  {
    "no": "01",
    "question": "What is WordPress?",
    "options": [
      "A blogging platform",
      "A content management system",
      "A web hosting service",
      "A programming language"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A content management system"
  },
  {
    "no": "02",
    "question": "Which programming language is primarily used to develop WordPress?",
    "options": ["PHP", "JavaScript", "Python", "Ruby"],
    "correctAnswer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "no": "03",
    "question": "What is a theme in WordPress?",
    "options": [
      "A collection of plugins",
      "A layout for a website",
      "A programming language",
      "A database management system"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A layout for a website"
  },
  {
    "no": "04",
    "question": "What is the purpose of a WordPress plugin?",
    "options": [
      "To change the website theme",
      "To add functionality to a WordPress site",
      "To manage user permissions",
      "To create backups of the website"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To add functionality to a WordPress site"
  },
  {
    "no": "05",
    "question": "Which of the following is the default database management system used by WordPress?",
    "options": ["MySQL", "MongoDB", "SQLite", "PostgreSQL"],
    "correctAnswer": "MySQL"
  },
  {
    "no": "06",
    "question": "What is the WordPress Dashboard?",
    "options": [
      "The front-end of a WordPress site",
      "The control panel for managing a WordPress site",
      "A plugin for WordPress development",
      "A theme for WordPress sites"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "The control panel for managing a WordPress site"
  },
  {
    "no": "07",
    "question": "What is the purpose of the WordPress shortcode?",
    "options": [
      "To secure the WordPress site",
      "To add custom functionality to posts and pages",
      "To change the website theme",
      "To manage user roles"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To add custom functionality to posts and pages"
  },
  {
    "no": "08",
    "question": "What is the function of the WordPress function 'wp_head()'?",
    "options": [
      "To display the website header",
      "To insert scripts and styles into the head section of the HTML document",
      "To create a new WordPress user",
      "To display the website footer"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To insert scripts and styles into the head section of the HTML document"
  },
  {
    "no": "09",
    "question": "What is the default permalink structure in WordPress?",
    "options": ["Plain", "Day and name", "Post name", "Custom structure"],
    "correctAnswer": "Plain"
  },
  {
    "no": "10",
    "question": "What is the role of the WordPress administrator?",
    "options": [
      "To manage the content of the website",
      "To install WordPress themes and plugins",
      "To perform routine maintenance tasks",
      "To have full control over the WordPress site"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "To have full control over the WordPress site"
  }
]
